

NISHA MORE

FRONT-END ENGINEER

My Contact

nisha.more2909@gmail.com

+91 7972630959

Nashik, Maharashtra, India

https://github.com/nishamore98

in www.linkedin.com/in/nishamore98/

https://nishamore.tech/

Skills

HTML 5 CSS SCSS MUI

JavaScript Redux ReactJS

Bootstrap Agile NPM

Tools

Figma Jira GIT & GitHub

VS Code Postman

Soft Skills

Creative Communication Skills

Team building Adaptive

Problem solving Collaborative

Education Background

 Matoshri College Of Engineering and Research center, Nashik - B.E. Electrical
 JUNE 2018 - AUG 2021
 CGPA - 7.46

Projects

-Smart mask vending machine and thermal body temperature monitoring, alert system with automatic sanitiser

-Dual input inverter (Solar & AC)

 K.K Wagh Women's Polytechnic, Nashik-Diploma in Electronics and Telecommunication JULY 2014 - JUNE 2018 CGPA - 7

About Me

A highly skilled front end software developer with 1.5 years of experience in developing and designing user-friendly websites and web applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and frameworks such as React and Redux. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to work well in a team.

Professional Experience

ITILITE Technologies - Frontend Engineer Nov 2021 - Feb 2023

Key responsibilities

- Created visually appealing and responsive user interfaces for the feature Client admin as behalf approver that provided a seamless user experience across various devices and platforms.
 200+ Users has given good feedback about the feature.
- Built the feature of transferring roles of users on deactivation.
 This feature led to a significant increase of 30% in user engagement also contributed in revenue growth.
- Built various reusable UI components and Published NPM packages. Successfully integrated third-party services into the system.
- Worked closely with designers, stakeholders and engineers to ensure that the design specifications for the feature Time based policy, document handler and admin notifications for new login request are accurately implemented in the user

ITILITE Technologies - Intern Frontend Engineer Aug 2021 - Oct 2021

Key responsibilities

- Image optimisation to improve website performance
- Created UI for showing YouTube video inside the modal
- Made UI changes & add anchors in existing UI
- Studied about React, created Test Route & Component
- Used react-data-table library to show data
- API integration
- Created UI for Help & Support page
- Created To Do list

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Marathi